[
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "cartegory": "science",
        "question": "What is the hottest planet?",
        "correct_answer": "Mercury",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Pluto",
            "Venus",
            "Saturn",
            "Mercury"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "cartegory": "animals",
        "question": "Which of the following birds is carnivorous?",
        "correct_answer": "Owl",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Pelican",
            "Owl",
            "Pigeon",
            "Turkey"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "cartegory": "programming",
        "question": "What is JSON?",
        "correct_answer": "Javascript Object Notation",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Java Object Notation",
            "Javascript Object Name",
            "Java Object Name",
            "Javascript Object Notation"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "cartegory": "programming",
        "question": "Which of the following is a Javascript framework?",
        "correct_answer": "Angular Js",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Node Js",
            "Jquery",
            "Laravel",
            "Angular Js"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "cartegory": "programming",
        "question": "Which of the following is a PHP framework?",
        "correct_answer": "Symfony",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "React",
            "Symfony",
            "Django",
            "Ruby"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "cartegory": "sports",
        "question": "Which european team has the highest amount of UEFA champions league trophies?",
        "correct_answer": "Real Madrid",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Arsenal",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Manchester United"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "cartegory": "sports",
        "question": "What was the final score between Barcelona and Sampdoria in the 1992 UEFA champions league final?",
        "correct_answer": "1-0",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "2-0",
            "3-1",
            "1-0",
            "2-1"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "cartegory": "programming",
        "question": "Which of the following is a CSS framework?",
        "correct_answer": "Bootstrap",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Slim",
            "Magento",
            "Bootstrap",
            "Amber"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "cartegory": "geography",
        "question": "Which of the following is a West African country?",
        "correct_answer": "Togo",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Uganda",
            "Togo",
            "Somalia",
            "Malawi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "cartegory": "programming",
        "question": "Which of the following is a server-side language?",
        "correct_answer": "Python",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Python",
            "HTML",
            "Ajax",
            "C++"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "cartegory": "animals",
        "question": "What is the fastest land animal?",
        "correct_answer": "Cheetah",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "Lion",
            "Hyena",
            "Cheetah",
            "Rabbit"
        ]
    }
]